# **Angela Robinette**

## **Front End Developer**

Email: <u>angela@dev-angela.com</u> Website: <u>https://dev-angela.com/</u> Phone: 406-671-1693

\* HTML \* CSS \* JavaScript \* Accessibility \* Security

#### **Profile:**

My coding journey began as a hobby in 2000. First, I worked with HTML and was hooked. A few years later, I learned CSS. Finally, I taught myself a bit of JavaScript for a hidden picture game.

I graduated from Purdue University Global - Summa Cum Laude - with an Associate degree in Software Development/Computer Programming. I love creating beautiful, functional web pages that enhance a user's experience and are secure and accessible to all. During my internship at PGIP-Tech, I was the software development lead. I went back afterward and became a mentor.

### **Education:**

**Purdue University Global** 

4.0 GPA Associate Degree Graduation – March 15, 2022

Montana State University Bozeman, MT

1994-1995 General Studies

**Montana State University** 

Billings, MT

1996-1997 English Major

**Colstrip High School** 

High School Diploma, Class of 1994

### **Experience:**

**PGIP-Tech Internship** 

January 2022 – Present SofDev Mentor

Dev-angela.com

January 2022 – Present Owner/Designer/Developer **PGIP-Tech Internship** 10/14/2021 – 12/21/2021

SofDev Manager

#### **Skills:**

HTML	CSS	<b>Paintshop</b>	JavaScript	Git	<b>Bootstrap</b>
15+ years	15+ years	Pro	10+ years	2+ years	1+ years
experience	experience	15+ years	experience	experience	experience
		experience			

## **Experience using:**

PHP	Docker	$\operatorname{SQL}$	C#	Angular